{"data":[{"question":"The secretary _____ all the letters by 12 o'clock.","a":"has typed","b":"will have typed","c":"will be typing","d":"will had typed","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by 12 o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time they come, we'll ______ dinner.","a":"have finished","b":"finish","c":"had finished","d":"finished","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of the century we will ______ most of the oxygen.","a":"had used up","b":"have used up","c":"have use up","d":"had use up","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of this century","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By 11 o'clock she'll ______ the shopping.","a":"have done","b":"has done","c":"have do","d":"has doing","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by 11 o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of the year I'll ______ four or five colds.","a":"have catched","b":"have caught","c":"had caught","d":"had catched","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of the year","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By 10 o'clock they ______ walking for 24 hours.","a":"will be","b":"will have","c":"will have been","d":"have been","answer":"3","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: 10 o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time they get to the theatre the play ______.","a":"will already start","b":"will have already started","c":"will be start","d":"will be started","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By dinner time he'll ______ reading the papers.","a":"have finished","b":"be finish","c":"be finished","d":"had finished","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by dinner time","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I _____ by the year 2020.","a":"will have retired","b":"will retire","c":"am retiring","d":"will be retire","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect: \n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future \n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP \n+ Sign word: by the year 2020 ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"By tea-lime he will ______ a packet of cigarettes.","a":"have smoked","b":"had smoked","c":"have smoke","d":"had smoke","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by tea-lime","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}